littlebigsnake.com 2019-10-24

# Little Big Snake: PRIVACY POLICY

Approved on November 1st, 2018.

This Policy for the processing of personal data (hereinafter referred to as the "Policy") is applicable to Software products (hereinafter referred to as the "Game", "Games") developed, published and/or administered under the control of "LittleBigSnake, Inc" ( located at the address: Suite 200, 15332 Antioch Street Los Angeles, California 90272, USA, hereinafter referred to as the "Company"), as well as other services of the Company, directly related to the Games, and approved by the Company's order issued on the 1st of November, 2018. 

### PREAMBLE

The company as part of its activities, namely, the publication, distribution and management of Games through the Internet, access information that is confidential, as well as accesses the personal data of individuals using the Games (hereinafter referred to as the "User".

The Company may need to obtain from the Users certain information and personal data for the purpose of properly identifying Users in the Games and meeting the terms of the User Agreement. In doing so, the Company confirms that such confidential information and/or data are subject to protection against unauthorized distribution.

### INFORMATION AND DATA OBTAINED BY THE COMPANY

By using the Games, including passing the registration procedure (if applicable), sending messages, letters and otherwise interacting with the Company, the User provides the Company with some information and data that are personal. Starting the use of the Games, the User agrees that the Company can collect, store and process the personal data of the Users, including the surname, first name, patronymic, photo (avatar in social networks), login, password, ID from social networks, IP-addresses , Cookie files, e-mail address for the purposes of executing the User Agreement.

The User undertakes not to collect, use or post personal data of third parties in the Game and any of its services without their consent, including surnames, names, patronymics, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, residential addresses, passport data or other information.

The User is responsible for the safety of his authorization data, including the login and password for accessing the User account in the Game or to any of its services.

It is not recommended for the User to communicate to third parties his personal data during the registration process and other actions performed with the use of the Games as well as other personal information, including telephone numbers, addresses, bank account numbers and other information and data that the User considers confidential.

The User agrees that in the process of managing the Games, the Company also receives certain technical and in-game information relating, in particular, to the User's activity when using the Games, including:

  * information about entering the Game (entry time and number of entries);
  * in-game locations visited by the User when using the Game;
  * acquired and (or) sold items in the course of using the Game;
  * use of activated and / or non-activated game data and commands;
  * missions (tasks) accepted by the User for execution;
  * missions (tasks) completed by the User;
  * the number of game actions committed by the User in conjunction with other Users;
  * the number of invitations sent by the User to other Users;
  * the amount of the User's virtual in-game currency;
  * the amount of earned and/or acquired virtual in-game currency.

### USE OF INFORMATION AND DATA OBTAINED BY THE COMPANY

The Company is entitled to use the information and data received from the User for the following purposes:

  * to manage the Account of the User;
  * to provide the User with access to the Games;
  * to provide the User with additional information and materials for the Games;
  * to provide the User with access to additional services, including services to which the User has subscribed; 
  * to ensure communication between Users;
  * for the customer support service;
  * to modify, supplement and improve the Games.

### COMMITMENT TO PRESERVE THE CONFIDENTIALITY AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION AND DATA

The Company undertakes to store information and data received from the User, taking all necessary legal, organizational and technical measures to protect such information and from unauthorized or accidental access to them, destruction, modification, blocking, copying, provision, distribution as well as from other illegal actions in respect of such information and personal data. The Company also undertakes to take all measures to prevent the disclosure or use of information and data in any other way, except as expressly provided in this Policy.

Access to the information of the User, including personal data, can only be obtained from employees, consultants and auditors of the Company who are required to access such information to perform their duties, with the necessary measures to protect the confidentiality of such information.

The Company has the right to disclose to third parties information and data provided by the User, only with the consent of the latter. The User agrees that the Company may disclose information about the User to third parties in the following cases:

  * to provide the User with additional information and services;
  * to ensure the financial operations carried out by the User when using the Games;
  * in the event that such disclosure is necessary for the administration of justice, the enforcement of a judicial act, under the act of another body or official subject to enforcement in accordance with the legislation of the United States. 

The Company keeps the information and personal data of the User until it is necessary for the purposes of executing the User Agreement, compliance with the requirements of the legislation, as well as execution of the relevant court decisions.

The person who is responsible for the processing of personal data in the Company: Name, position, e-mail.

### RECEIVING AND USE OF CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION AND DATA RECEIVED FROM MINORS

The Company, acting in good faith, does not accept or collect intentionally any information and data on persons who have not reached the age specified by the legislation of their country of residence (location), to use services similar to the Games developed and/or under the administration (control) of the Company, including the name, surname, address, telephone number and/or e-mail address.

The persons who have not reached the specified age can not use the Games as well as provide their information and data without the consent of the parents or the persons who replace them.

### TECHNICAL INFORMATION (cookies)

Cookies are used (cookies mean small files that are stored on the user's computer and contain information about the last operation of the User) in the Games developed and/or controlled by the Company in order to facilitate the authorization procedure, remember the language that the User uses when using Games.

The Company has the right to publish cookies and web beacons on its website and on the Games’ Websites to collect information about the sections that the User has visited, about the Games and services that the User is interested in, and about the User's movements through the Games and Company sites. If the User is registered, this information is stored in the Company's database. The company uses this information to improve the functionality of the Games, to provide Users with additional information and services as well as for other marketing purposes.

The User has the right to independently regulate the use of cookies in the browser that she/he uses. In this case, disabling the use of cookies, the User in some cases will not be able to fully use all the functions of the game.

### ACTION OF THIS POLICY AND RESOURCES OF THIRD PARTIES

The provisions of this Policy apply only to Games developed, published and/or controlled by the Company. At the same time, the Company specifically stipulates that in some games hyperlinks and banners belonging to third parties are used, including those that lead to third-party sites. The Company does not guarantee the User's compliance with the provisions of this Policy on such sites and is not responsible for the disclosure by the User of confidential information and/or personal data on such sites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here (<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>) 

### USER ACCESS AND CHANGE OF INFORMATION AND DATA

The User has the right to access all his personal information and data stored in the Company's databases. The User has the right to prohibit the Company from using the information and data mentioned in this Policy by writing a letter to the Company's e-mail address: support@littlebigsnake.com. However, after receiving such a prohibition from the User, the Company can not guarantee the User will have unimpeded and full access to the Games and other services of the Company.

Information and data may be changed by the User at any time subject to the restrictions mentioned in this Policy.

### AMENDMENTS TO THE POLICY AND APPLICABLE LAW

The Company reserves the right to amend this Policy at any time, including due to changes in law.

This Policy as well as any disputes that may arise between the User and the Company are governed by the legislation of the United States without regard to conflicts of law and regardless of the location of the User.
